WE ARE ALL TRYING HERE
Before enlisting, I had five million won,
so I put it into stocks.
When I got discharged…
Ta-da.
It increased to 30 million.
Yes, 30 million.
Right then,
do you know what my biggest worry was?
"I'm the only one
who knows about this money."
"What if I die?"
Then one day…
a burglar tried to break in.
I saw something like a knife,
and my heart started pounding.
I didn't know what to do.
At that moment,
I thought of the 30 million won I had.
I thought, "I can't die."
"I have 30 million won."
Even though I hadn't eaten or slept,
I was full of energy.
That 30 million won
made me feel like I had superpowers.
But then…
it increased to 50 million won.
Suddenly,
everything became easy.
It felt like
nothing in life stood in my way.
Dong-man.
Let's step into the center…
of history.
Hey, Hwang.
Want to try taking a photo?
You were such a beautiful young man.
I'll bear that in mind.
I can see the universe in your face.
From what angle and in what way
can I capture
the depth of the universe inside you?
I ponder over this every day
while watching all of your films.
He really is a crazy bastard.
After watching you every day,
I'm beginning to mix up your face
with mine.
HWANG DONG-MAN: HEHEHE
Seriously, this little punk.
MR. NOH KANG-SIK
Stop messaging me.
Who does he think he is?
How dare you have the audacity
to babble on like that?
Yes, sir!
I got excited
because I have the top actor Noh Kang-sik
in my contacts.
Damn it.
That's it for today.
Jeez.
Director, let's take five.
DEPOSIT AMOUNT: 20,000,000 WON
SENDER: HWANG DONG-MAN
What's this?
You're saving 100 million won
to give Yeong-sil when you see her.
I'm going to chip in.
I got my signing fee.
My film's going into production.
DEPOSIT AMOUNT: 20,000,000 WON
SENDER: HWANG JIN-MAN
Why?
If you have money,
get your own place and move out.
Live your own life,
and don't worry about mine.
Can't you let me feel grand for once?
I felt grand all night
thinking about chipping in.
Don't stomp on my grandeur.
Don't send it.
We might not even find her!
Of course, we'll find her!
If we can't find her, she'll find you!
Don't you think she wants to see her dad?
Are you meeting someone?
I'll get going now.
I'll come back tomorrow.
All right, go on.
It's cold. Why didn't you wait inside?
I just got here.
You always say that.
Your nose is red.
I really did just get here.
Now that Noh Kang-sik is on board,
I'm worried it might be too successful.
How will I handle everyone's envy
and jealousy?
Park Gyeong-se is probably
seething with envy right now.
What do I even do when I see his face?
Also,
what if I become so successful
that I suddenly lose my "nobody" charm?
I'm scatterbrained and all over the place,
but I'm not unhappy.
This is my identity and charm.
If I become too successful,
I'm afraid I'll suddenly lose my charm.
You know what I mean.
It's like a character
who starts out as a charming troublemaker
but becomes serious and dull
toward the end.
I'm afraid I'll end up dull like that.
Isn't it weird
how all successful people are dull?
Of all the pointless worries
I've heard so far,
this is the most pointless one.
Right?
Even if I succeed,
I'll still be a scatterbrained, crazy guy
who's all over the place.
I'm going to be successful too.
Will I lose my charm as well?
Wait. Are you saying I'll lose it?
I wouldn't say you'll lose it.
-It's just…
-It's just what?
You'll become less approachable.
It's difficult enough
to approach you right now.
Oh, I don't mean
you're uncomfortable to be around.
It's like
you're on a completely
different level from me.
I still remember how shocked I was
the first time I saw you.
It was like seeing an ideal face
sent from heaven.
"Let this be called a face."
"This is a face,
so let all faces resemble it."
They can resemble it,
but they can never be the same.
The moment they become the same,
it's no longer ideal.
An ideal is something
you can never fully achieve.
That's what it means, right?
That's the kind of face I saw.
It feels like a miracle
sitting here talking to you
when you once felt unapproachable.
On top of that, you write well.
Can you stop being so perfect?
You almost feel unreal.
Are you worshipping me?
You're an ideal sent down by the gods,
so of course, you deserve worship.
You know your share is included
in the money I received, right?
Tell me whatever it is you want.
Don't say "nothing."
Or "anything."
If I buy whatever I please,
you might end up with something bizarre.
I want to receive a bizarre gift.
Oh, no, no, no.
Stop being all lovey-dovey
and hurry up already!
-Jeez.
-Hi!
-Hello.
-Hey.
I'm freezing.
What are we having?
Let's have something fancy
with green stuff sprinkled on top.
I don't like food like that.
They say women like that kind of food.
How much are you spending?
How much should I spend?
-I know a place. Let's go.
-What?
Don't worry. It's not expensive.
By the way, are you heading
to the police station or something?
I probably will soon.
I'm trying out the outfit in advance.
Police-station vibe.
Police-station look.
We could've gone somewhere more expensive!
-It's expensive here!
-Hello.
-Hey, nachos!
-Thank you.
Enjoy.
Hi, Mom.
Yeah.
Grandma gets discharged next week.
She's okay.
She can walk a bit now.
Mom, I'm out right now,
so I'll call you when I get home.
Bye.
I thought you said
you were on bad terms with your mom.
She's my stepmom.
You have a stepmom too?
Then what about your grandmother?
She's my stepmom's mom.
Then what about your dad?
He passed away.
When did he pass away?
When I was in the 8th grade.
Have the three of you
lived together ever since?
Yes.
My stepmom is mostly in Japan for work.
They sound like good people.
And you're a good person too.
You see, a relationship doesn't last
if only one side is good.
I get it.
Even in a newly formed family,
you don't become strangers overnight
just because a connection is lost.
You shared a life, after all.
Oh Jeong-hui and I
lost our connection a long time ago.
And my dad…
has a lot of problems.
This mother-daughter relationship
might end at any moment now.
There's a chance
my name…
will be all over the internet.
I just hope I don't get too scared.
All right.
I'll take on
all the misfortune in the world,
so make it big, okay?
All of you make it big, okay?
Hwang Dong-man.
Byeon Eun-a.
Lee Jun-hwan.
Everyone, make it big!
-Make it big!
-Oh, come on!
-Don't lie!
Come on, you're exaggerating!
Jeez, they're laughing so damn loud.
Be quiet.
We can't be outdone!
-One, two, three!
-Two, three!
The name of a target appeared, but…
NATIONAL STRESS MANAGEMENT DEPARTMENT
It's the country's
most notorious nutcase politician
who's raising everyone's blood pressure
and must be taken out quickly.
But…
it's his wife.
She might be a nutcase,
but she's still his wife.
He can't just let her die, can he?
But then
she says the one line
that really pisses off the protagonist
and makes him say, "Screw it. Just die."
What could it be?
What did you say?
When will the script be ready?
We were supposed to give them
episodes three and four ages ago.
Stop struggling with them.
Just hand them over and get it over with.
I could think of so many moments
that would piss off the protagonist
if he were a writer.
Why did I make him
a Grade 9 civil servant?
Say what?
His friend gets flagged as a target.
All of the memories
and history they shared
flash before his eyes.
He gets choked up. He can't stand it.
He's trying to save them,
but then they ask,
"When will the script be ready?"
"What the… What did you just say?"
"'When will the script be ready?'"
He told them not to say that one thing,
but they said it anyway.
He tells them,
"I'm talking to you right now,
but 99% of my brain
is focused on the script."
"I'm running on the last 1% of my brain,
doing everything I can to keep you alive,
but it's no use."
"Just go."
"Take care."
"I can't see you off."
There are so many moments
when writers get so pissed off
that they just give up.
I just thought of a rage trigger
for the protagonist!
"You only make two million won a month?"
That's it.
That's it. You're a genius, Writer Park.
You figured it out.
You're a genius.
This is it.
"You only make two million won a month?"
"The protagonist is filled with rage
and finally comes to a decision."
-Bang!
-Bang! And they're dead.
He fires nonstop. All right.
Hold on. Let's think here.
"The protagonist starts shooting
to an excessive degree."
"You only make two million won a month?"
"Only two million won a month?"
"There's no point in drawing this out…"
Make it big, Hwang Dong-man!
Thank you.
-Make it big!
-Thank you! I'll do my best!
Make it big, Eun-a.
-Make it big.
-Everyone, make it big.
Let's go!
Where are we going?
-Where is she going?
-Where?
Where are we going?
Mi-ran!
No! Don't do this, Mi-ran.
-Why not?
-Please don't.
He'll beat me to death.
Okay, okay.
Let's leave.
Don't!
Hwang Dong-man!
She went in!
What do we do?
Just as I expected,
you've been drinking.
I had a drink myself.
There was no other way for me to wipe away
the wrong that remains somewhere.
I stopped by because I wanted to see you.
She's back.
This is why I told you not to go in.
Just you wait!
You'll be into me before you know it.
Wait for me!
The ball goes to the goalkeeper,
Choi Chun-ho.
It got cut off.
Yes, the pass came up short.
But the pressure continues.
If you file a lawsuit
and the media gets hold of this,
it's a given that both sides
will get screwed.
I don't care if we both get screwed.
It's not just you two.
-What about Jung Hyeon-u?
-He has nothing to do with this!
It was a fight between Jang Mi-ran and me.
You think she'll stay quiet
about why you guys fought?
She'll disclose every last detail.
Jang Mi-ran was 100% at fault
for what she did.
We'll make her apologize,
so let's settle this for 100 million won.
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT
You think I'm doing this for money?
You know what?
Even if I killed her,
it still wouldn't be enough!
Even if it means humiliating myself
by admitting
I got beaten up like an idiot,
I'm going to take Jang Mi-ran down
for good.
I'll never accept a payoff
and pretend it never happened.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Of course, we'll file a lawsuit, but…
Let's do it a bit later.
My drama is out right now,
and I'm going to Taiwan next week
to promote it.
Jung Hyeon-u is a fool.
He should've insisted on
going after Jang Mi-ran.
This makes things difficult.
What makes a woman
grab another woman by their hair?
I've seen it in dramas
but never in real life.
I regret it too.
Grabbing her hair was lame.
Next time,
I'll hit her with a roundhouse kick.
Don't be so stubborn.
You may never get to act again.
You know,
I just want it all out in the open.
I want everything revealed
about how this whole mess started
and put it out there for the world to see.
"Jung Hyeon-u…
liked…
Jang Mi-ran."
"Jang Mi-ran…
isn't…
a crazy bitch."
-Tell them I want to see them.
-I will.
What about the Knock knock knock contract?
It'll come through soon.
Welcome.
Come in.
Take a seat.
Here, try this.
I wondered why you never backed down
when I was on your case
and what made you act so defiant.
You had an ace up your sleeve.
When did you start writing?
Have you written a lot?
No.
How many have you written?
Not many.
I knew it.
I have a good eye for things.
I called you "Ax," didn't I?
Golden Ax.
There was something different
about the things you said
compared to other producers.
There are things only someone
who's actually written can say.
If you haven't written, you wouldn't know.
Let's keep the fact that you're Yeong-sil
just between you and me.
You know that Ma Jae-yeong
desperately tried to hide you, right?
And it's not like I don't know why
he tried to do so.
He's already on edge as it is.
Nothing good will come
from provoking the director.
Knock knock knock will go under his name,
and he'll pay you.
And let's sign
a separate writer's contract.
I'll pay you top rate.
You know me.
I never miss out on a sure bet.
I'll only write
when I have something to write.
I won't write for money.
You're so cool.
But you know,
writing comes from
the sense of repaying a debt.
You know Writer Park who wrote The Fools?
After gambling away their signing fee,
they couldn't pay up,
so they wrote nonstop and came up with it.
It ended up being a big hit.
Money makes writing happen.
Without money, it doesn't happen.
How about 100 million won per screenplay?
Let's sign a contract for just two.
You don't have to come to work,
but you can if you want.
Do whatever suits you.
So Writer Park caused a stir overseas too.
Later on,
they wrote it all.
Seasons two, three, and even four.
Hey.
The doors are closing.
Are you on your way back from lunch?
Yes. Looks like you are too.
Yeah.
The key crew is set now, right?
We just need to confirm
the production designer today.
I see.
Why did he act like
he was hiding something?
He looked flustered, right?
I'm not really sure.
What's the deal with them eating together?
-Who?
-Mr. Choi and Byeon Eun-a.
It smelled like they had barbecue.
Really?
ALL THE LUCK TO THE CAST AND CREW
OF VILLAIN HUNT
SUPPORTING NOH KANG-SIK!
FROM HWANG DONG-MAN, KO HYE-JIN
-Please enjoy!
-Thank you.
They built the set well.
Do a better job, you punk!
Give me a break.
"Give me a break"?
You think I don't know what you do?
You intimidate your juniors
to knock them off their game.
-Hello.
-What's wrong?
If your co-star does a good job,
-you do whatever you can
-They got into a fight.
to make sure that scene doesn't get used.
Wow, Jeong-min's good at acting.
He's not acting.
Hey.
Tell me.
You think you're a good actor?
Yes.
Does a good actor
cut off their co-star's flow
and do whatever they want?
You're not confident in your acting!
That's why you're all over the place!
Or maybe it's your old-school acting style
that can't keep up with my range
as an actor.
Are you kidding me?
Let's just focus on acting, okay?
Just acting,
not this hierarchy bullshit.
Hey, show some respect.
Got it?
Goddamn it.
Screw this. I'm done here.
Do you really fucking
expect me to shoot this
while getting beaten up at my age?
I'll pay whatever penalty and quit.
It's disgusting how this whole industry
keeps quiet because of guys like him.
I'll call every reporter I know,
tell them all the crap you've pulled,
and leave this industry.
Someone like you should've been
blacklisted a long time ago.
You know that?
Go right ahead.
Do it.
Go ahead and call the reporters, you punk!
Call them now!
Let go of me!
-I said let go of me!
-Hit me.
-Let go of me, you jerks!
-Hit me!
-Go ahead! Hit me!
-Hey!
Hey, stop, stop.
Please calm down.
I mean…
This?
How is this a hit?
Who the hell are you?
I'm sorry.
I get that you're offended.
Then why don't you
just make him feel the same way?
Just do this and make him feel offended.
Come on, it's not that hard to do.
How is this hard?
Have you lost your mind too, you punk?
See? You can see on his face
that he's offended.
-I'm sorry.
-I mean…
-I'm sorry. Let's go.
-Wait, Hye-jin. Hold on.
I don't get it. Why are you getting mad
because he offended you?
You just need to offend him right back!
Why would you threaten to quit
and talk to reporters
over something like this?
Again, who the hell are you?
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
-I said let's go!
-I heard you!
Call the reporters,
but at least wait until after my film!
Wait until I'm done with my film!
Come on, don't you agree?
Do you know how hard I worked
to get to this point?
That's enough, you bastard!
I ought to just…
You know what?
-I'm not offended.
-For goodness' sake.
What's there to get offended about?
When I tell people
that Hwang Dong-man is the director
and the lead actor is Noh Kang-sik,
everyone says the same thing.
"Oh no, Ms. Ko."
"That'll take years off your life."
I refuse to work myself into anything
that leads to cancer.
Remember what I said?
I plan to live to 100.
If I think it might give me cancer,
I'll scrap it immediately.
So just shut up and stay still!
Don't do anything or say anything!
And don't step in.
Nothing improves when you step in!
Just say, "Ready, action, cut." Okay?
Okay.
Why did you and Mr. Choi
have lunch together out of nowhere?
Did you tell him you're quitting?
He goes hard on people, but the second
someone says they're quitting,
he softens up
and tries to talk them out of it.
What did you two talk about?
Why do you want to know?
Are you anxious
that he's doting on me again?
Watch your mouth, will you?
I'm your senior.
So what?
You can talk to me however you want?
You could've just said
that you somehow ended up eating together.
The way you asked me didn't allow for
such a casual response.
You were being snide.
I won't let her get away with this.
Why does Mr. Choi listen to that brat?
She's against changing the protagonist
of Knock knock knock to a woman?
Who does she think she is?
Even the director approved it,
so who the hell is she to object?
Goddamn it.
You've made a lot of progress
in developing it.
Yes, I did.
Let's put a hold on
Jang Mi-ran's contract.
Why all of a sudden?
This is under wraps
because of her current drama,
but something big is about to drop.
What is it?
A criminal lawsuit.
For assault.
I don't think we can cast
Oh Jeong-hui either.
Damn it.
And we don't have Noh Kang-sik.
We can't do Knock knock knock
without Oh Jeong-hui.
Put a hold on her contract for now.
MS. OH JEONG-HUI
This is a mess.
Hello, Ms. Oh!
Right, yes.
Goodness, we're not stalling.
Of course, we want you.
Absolutely.
It's nothing major,
but there's been some talk
about changing the protagonist to a woman
since it'll shift the mood entirely.
The writer did.
Yes, Yeong-sil.
We can't completely ignore
what the writer says.
The moment Hyo-jin opens her mouth,
I'm bored to death.
Every single word is boring.
She seems like someone
who'll never open up,
no matter how long you know her.
She's not someone
who intentionally hides what's inside…
but someone who doesn't know
how to communicate what's inside.
How can a person like that
be in filmmaking?
I'm in The Eight Club with her,
but I've only talked to her
for maybe ten minutes at most.
-It's awkward when I'm alone with her.
-Right?
Yes.
When she starts talking,
I hate the thought of the sound
of her voice touching me in any way,
-so my body just stiffens up.
-Right.
-And I can't hear anything.
-It's like my ears automatically shut off.
-I hate it.
But when I talk to you,
it feels like we have a real conversation.
I'm so moved.
People always say I talk nonstop
and that I can't hold a conversation.
You do talk nonstop.
Right.
When we meet,
you do 80% of the talking on your own.
Right, on my own.
But it's never boring.
Everything you say really hits me.
And my ears open up.
Sometimes, it's to the point
where I want to take notes.
I had planned
to keep my mouth shut for a while
because I got really chewed out today.
No, don't keep your mouth shut.
Yes, ma'am! I won't keep my mouth shut!
At least, not in front of you.
I feel like I can finally breathe
when I talk to you.
It feels like everything you say
is what I would say,
and you always seem to understand
exactly what I mean.
I'd always get nervous
when talking to people.
I'd wonder,
"How are they taking what I'm saying?"
But when I'm with you,
it feels like my heart bursts open
and everything flows out smoothly
without any hesitation.
I feel the same.
Everything you say
feels like what I would say.
Do you think
we were meant to be one person,
but got split into two
and came into the world?
I would've liked you
even if you were a man,
or even if you were a tree.
And if you were the wind,
I would've been nuts about you.
Eun-a,
you're too precious to be held
within such a small frame
and a confined space.
I want the whole world
to be Byeon Eun-a.
It's Byeon Eun-a.
Eun-a?
Why did you get so small?
Oh dear.
Please take good care of Eun-a.
Oh, Eun-a! Oh no! Eun-a!
Eun-a…
You know,
you give off a teenage boy vibe.
Is that a compliment?
A huge one.
Eun-a.
-Eun-a.
Welcome.
Just a second. I'll bring more drinks.
Oh, hello.
-It's been a while.
-Yes, it has.
I hear you're debuting soon?
I've actually been meaning to tell you.
After all, you're the reason I'm here,
and you taught me how to write.
So I really wanted to tell you
that I was debuting.
Thank you!
I worked with Ms. Oh for a bit
a long time ago.
It was
a very embarrassing memory,
so I don't usually talk about it.
I worked on the directing team
for Dogs and Cats.
Oh, this is Producer Byeon Eun-a
from Choi Film.
Let me introduce…
Sit down.
Right, let's sit down.
-Would you like a drink--
-No, thank you.
I heard the writer of Knock knock knock
is against casting me in the role.
I'd like to know why you're against it,
Ms. Yeong-sil.
Are you against
changing the protagonist to a woman,
or are you against me playing the role?
Just give it to me straight.
That's why I'm here.
She wouldn't be
against it.
Right?
Which is scarier?
A crazy woman or a crazy man?
Between a crazy woman and a crazy man
roaming the streets,
which is scarier?
Wouldn't a strong man who could harm me…
be scarier?
Which is scarier?
A female ghost or a male ghost?
Fear…
is an emotional state,
not a physical one.
If strong men are scary,
are all horror film protagonists
supposed to be men?
I thought you were savvy,
but you're surprisingly narrow-minded.
Your objection to changing
to a female protagonist isn't valid.
Is there a personal reason
you object to casting me?
Because it's sickening.
That disgusting ambition of yours
that knows no limits
and keeps pushing its way in.
I want you to know
you can't have everything.
No matter how good they act,
the actor's own emotions
still come through.
It's always a battle.
You have to outshine others.
It's always more, more, more.
Have you ever acted in a supporting role?
Have you ever once enjoyed working?
Enjoy working? Do I look like an amateur?
I believe Daniel Day-Lewis
worked as a shoemaker.
You have to reach the end
to know there's nothing special
before you take a different path.
Don't tell me to become a shoemaker
when I haven't even reached
the end of my path yet.
If someone says money isn't a big deal,
do you agree and give in?
It's not too late to make money
and come to that decision on your own.
It's the same thing.
You have to reach the end of hell to know.
Do you even know what hell is?
You can go through hell
at just nine years old.
I don't know.
It's taboo to talk about her.
Oh, I know her name.
It's Byeon Si-on.
Which sounds better,
Byeon Si-on or Byeon Eun-a?
It's not true. Right, Eun-a?
Take a look at every line you've written
and your desire to kill in each one.
Your motivation is fueled
by your hatred for me.
They say you can't blame parents
once you turn 40.
What will you use as motivation then?
How's your grandmother doing?
Anyone who absolutely detests something
also has something they absolutely love.
It's how they live on.
As soon as I was born,
I was abandoned every day.
Your deep sigh,
your look…
Even if it kills me…
I want to show you how wrong you were.
Just write it all down and give it to me.
Write down everything you remember
about how much of a bitch I was.
You can write a hundred pages
or a thousand, and I'll read it.
I'll read it every day
like it's a daily Bible verse.
I'll repent while reading it.
I'll spend the rest of my life
dwelling on that precious wound
you can't seem to let go!
So you just write it down
and be done with it!
Some writers keep reliving their own pain.
You used all of your hatred for me
in writing Knock knock knock.
There's nothing left to write about it,
so just let it go and move on!
Stop rehashing the same emotions
and letting your writing get rusty!
The next round will reveal
what kind of writing Ma Jae-yeong produces
and what kind of writing
Yeong-sil produces.
It'll determine who Knock knock knock
originally belonged to.
You used all of your hatred for me
in writing Knock knock knock.
There's nothing left to write about it,
so just let it go and move on!
If you could erase your childhood memories
to escape from this pain,
would you do it?
No.
Without this pain, that woman…
would be completely innocent.
She was neglected
and grew up without her parents.
I didn't think much of it at the time,
but looking back now,
my heart simply goes out to her.
I wonder what she's doing now
and how her life is going.
That sloppy gimbap
she clearly made herself.
I still think about that sad gimbap
and how she forced it down.
NO WAY, LOOK AT THIS
POOR THING… THE KID DIDN'T DESERVE THIS
Has it ever occurred to you
that it might be rude
to post something like this?
This child is now an adult.
How would she feel reading this?
What about the pain
of having to relive a childhood
that everyone remembers as pitiful?
You may act sympathetic,
but right now,
you're keeping her trapped
in that painful past and toying with her.
Please don't pretend it's compassion.
Don't pretend it's compassion,
you assholes.
NATIONAL STRESS MANAGEMENT DEPARTMENT
EPISODE 4
BY PARK GYEONG-SE, PARK JEONG-MIN
-Hey.
-Did you read the script?
Yeah.
What do you think?
It's fun.
That's it?
What else should I say?
Is it really fun?
Yeah, it is.
Then why are you talking like that?
How should I be talking?
I say it's fun, and you still complain.
Are you attending
Director Lee's premiere later?
No, I want to sleep.
Come to the after-party, then.
Forget it. I'm sleeping.
Bye.
"TRAPPED IN WRONG ANSWERS" AFTER-PARTY
-Hello.
-Why didn't Director Park Gyeong-se come?
-He was up all night, so he's sleeping.
That's a shame. I had a lot to ask him.
Okay, then.
Does your company produce
period pieces as well?
Wait.
Director Park!
Why are you so late?
I was tired so I almost didn't make it.
Oh, really?
Have you eaten?
Please excuse me for a second.
-Feels like quite the party.
-Please dig in.
Oh, hello.
It's very interesting, huh?
Isn't it weird, though?
But I think it'll do well.
Are you sure about that?
Oh, it's Ms. Ko.
Ms. Ko!
When did you get here?
Who are you, sir?
Come on. Are you drunk?
Do you know me?
I don't think we've met before.
What are you doing?
What's with the acting?
Excuse me, but I don't know who you are.
I believe you've got the wrong person.
Can you please leave?
Director Park,
I thought you couldn't come.
Episodes three and four are amazing!
They're more fun than the first two.
That's good to hear.
Everyone in the company is raving about
how National Stress Management Department
has been confirmed
as a long-running series.
You have to sign
a three-season deal with us, okay?
Goodness, three seasons? Come on.
-Just think about it.
-I will.
Excuse me.
Are you Director Park Gyeong-se who wrote
National Stress Management Department?
So you're the one who wrote that.
I'm so sorry for not recognizing you.
Why are you acting like this?
I really enjoyed reading it.
I've read all of your work,
but I think this is your best yet.
I'm sure it'll do well.
Your writing
was full of excitement.
So full of energy!
You must be in love.
Your writing was full of excitement.
For creators,
people are their greatest asset.
Like slash-and-burn farmers
who burn their land to cultivate again,
creators can completely fall for someone
and soak up their words,
their energy,
and everything about them
to get back on their feet.
That's why I think
creators should be allowed to fall in love
a hundred, a thousand times.
I'll support you.
Keep writing with that same excitement
to the very end.
Good luck.
Honey.
Hye-jin.
Damn it.
Ko Hye-jin.
They say the most pitiful person…
is the wife of a director.
But I'm also…
the CEO of a production company.
So be excited.
Keep being excited.
Just write well.
I don't care if you fall into hell
or into a honeypot.
As long as you come back
with some writing,
I'll drag you into hell or shove you
straight into that damn honeypot myself!
So just keep being excited.
Fine, I got excited!
I met a woman who looked at me
the way Ko Hye-jin used to,
so I got excited!
You don't even dote on me anymore!
So how do you expect me to write?
I didn't know what to do,
so I got hammered and went to sleep.
When I got up,
it was dark outside.
Depression presses down on me
like a heavy iron weight.
Who the hell are you
to object to casting Oh Jeong-hui?
You even went behind my back
and told Mr. Choi that you're Yeong-sil.
I'm scrapping this. I won't do it.
I won't!
Speak slowly. I'll hear you out.
The more you run your mouth,
the better it is for me
since I'm recording this.
Overconfident bastard.
You're working on a project
worth hundreds of billions of won
with a bunch of A-list actors,
and you make a call like this
without thinking?
Your voice needs to be
kept on record forever,
so the world never forgets
what kind of person you are.
Someone like you
never should've been born.
Don't come.
The food here is fine. Just get some rest.
I'll go tomorrow.
Lie down.
Go on, lie down.
Watch some TV.
Okay?
I have to give it to you.
You've got a knack for picking up
whatever I throw away.
You picked up Noh Kang-sik, the grant,
and Byeon Eun-a.
Shouldn't you be thanking me
at this point?
You think you sound cool
saying you threw them away?
Just be honest.
You were afraid,
so you deliberately
let go of them.
She shone so brightly,
and you got so scared
that you deliberately
let go of Byeon Eun-a.
Who got scared?
Who shines?
Who?
-Tell me.
-I'm freaking scared too.
But I endure it.
Even if I go blind
from her shiny brightness,
I'm going to keep both eyes open
and endure it.
That's the respect you owe someone
who believes in you, you jackass.
No matter how scared you were,
you shouldn't have turned so evil
when you ran away from her first!
Goddamn it!
Freaking loser. Who do you think you are?
To hell with my movie.
If I don't take you on today,
I'm a freaking moron.
I'll kill you!
Damn it.
You think Byeon Eun-a is someone
you can just throw away?
You can't throw away an ideal
sent by the gods!
You can't!
Just say, "Byeon Eun-a did it!"
"Byeon Eun-a did it!"
Cover the whole world with Byeon Eun-a!
That's the only way
you can escape the hell you're in!
I did it!
I'm the one who did it!
By the way,
I'm really sorry to say this,
but why does your identity
as Oh Jeong-hui's hidden daughter,
something you find so painful,
feel and look so shiny and bright to me?
I'm just an ordinary person
who can never catch up to you.
Ms. Byeon Eun-a.
It seems
you're determined to rise to the heavens.
God.
Please dote on me.
CLOSED UNTIL THE END OF DECEMBER
What happened?
I was duped.
This leather…
was made in 1998.
The story
about it being worn
by a Russian soldier in World War II…
was a lie.
A lie.
I thought about the Russian soldier
who was shot and killed
and spent my days living
with a tragic sense of purpose.
But I got duped by a handsome guy
at a flea market.
It turns out, even handsome guys lie.
But you know what?
For some reason…
I feel relieved.
I think my life will be
one big comedy to the end,
so I feel relieved.
The protagonist in Joker
thought his life was a tragedy,
but when he found it was a comedy,
he went off the rails.
However…
I like
that it's a comedy.
Life should be a comedy.
Would you mind
if I did a classic comedy bit?
Guess where my tooth is?
It only feels right to do this
since I've lost my tooth.
WE ARE ALL TRYING HERE
Just so you know,
it's not just women at Eun-a's house.
If you mess with Eun-a,
you'll be in real trouble.
Let's just stop, Dong-man.
I was just saying it for fun.
Let's end this. Damn it.
You can probably do it
without the emotion watch now.
You should give it a try.
Practice accurately identifying emotions.
Why isn't Writer Park here?
Just ignore me and keep writing
with that same excitement.
I'm Director Hwang Dong-man.
Dong-man has gone quiet.
I think he's having a mental breakdown.
Start filming already, you bastard!
Start filming!
Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim